- You're over-thinking this.
- No, I'm not.
(Penny:)- You always over-think things.
- There you go. "Always" made it worse.
(Penny:)See, this is where everything
goes wrong, when we talk.
(Leonard:)Well, I don't know how you have
a relationship without talking.
I went out with T.J. for eight months.
We never talked.
(Penny:)To this day, I don't even know
what T.J. stands for.
Wait, if you guys didn't talk?...
Never mind, stupid question.
(Sheldon:)And now that I have some wood...
(Sheldon:)...I'm going to begin the erection
of my settlement.
(Raj:)He's got to be doing this on purpose.
Ooh, eight-thirty. You and Penny decide
to go out and paint the town beige?
You're 30 years old
and you live with your mother.
(Raj:)I guess it didn't go well.
(Sheldon:)We don't know that. Not to a certainty.